A high-voltage thriller!
Demolition High is a action film directed by Jim Wynorski.
When a group of terrorists (led by Luther) take over a high school making the students in it their hostages, it is up to several of the students
(led by Lenny) to help prevent disaster while the authorities (Slater and General Wainwright) do their part on the other side.
Lenny Slater, played by Corey Haim.
Slater, played by Alan Thicke.
General Wainwright, played by Dick Van Patten.
Luther, played by Jeff Kober.
Tanya, played by Melissa Brasselle.
Stacy, played by Kimberley Roberts.
Demolition Man is a 1993 American science fiction action film
directed by Marco Brambilla in his directorial debut.
It stars Sylvester Stallone, Wesley Snipes, Sandra Bullock, and Nigel Hawthorne.
Stallone plays John Spartan, a risk-taking police officer with a
reputation for causing destruction while carrying out his work.
After a failed attempt to rescue hostages from evil crime lord Simon Phoenix
(Snipes), they are both sentenced to be cryogenically frozen in 1996.
In 2032, Phoenix escapes and the authorities awaken Spartan to help capture him.
The story makes allusions to many other works, including Aldous
Huxley's 1932 dystopian novel Brave New World and H.
Wells's The Sleeper Awakes.
The film was released in the United States on October
8, 1993, to mixed reviews from critics.
It earned $159 million worldwide, and was
considered a successful film for Stallone.